In the ring of death, only one man can be king!
The King of the Kickboxers is a action, crime,
thriller film directed by Lo Yuen-Ming.
Jake, a New York policeman  poses as an actor to expose the
making of martial-arts death movies in Thailand.
Jake Donahue, played by Loren Avedon.
Khan, played by Billy Blanks.
Prang, played by Keith Cooke.
Drug Dealer, played by Jerry Trimble.
Captain O'Day, played by Richard Jaeckel.
Anderson, played by Don Stroud.
The King of the Kickboxers (also known as Karate Tiger V and No Retreat, No Surrender 4) is a 1990 martial arts
film directed by Lucas Lowe and starring Loren Avedon as Jake Donahue and Billy Blanks as Khan.
The film explores themes of martial arts, fighter,
bangkok, thailand, snuff, training.
The tone is emotional and intense.